flashgamehole.com 2018-08-23

# Minigames | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the MiniGames.com website and online services. By accessing MiniGames.com, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes what kind of information MiniGames.com collect from users and how we store it and use it.

Our visitors privacy is important to us and should be protected. Children visitors should always advise their parents or guardians before entering information on any website and we strongly believe that families should set guidelines regarding online sharing of personal information.

In MiniGames.com there is some information collected from traffic references of hosting server and from cookies. Traffic references of hosting servers is information like for example internet domain, IP address, day and time of visit, location, type of browser and operating system used to access our site, pages you visit and how long you spend. This information known as site visitors statistics is used only to improve our services to you.

MiniGames.com may use cookies to improve the use of our website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in your computer’s web browser and used broadly by all websites. It is used only to personalize your experience on websites. Next time you revisit a website, this site will know your previous activity.

We do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name, IP address and such and most certainly we do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer. Most of browsers default setting is to accept cookies but you have the option to be notified if you want to receive a cookie or not. 

We use analytics service providers to analyze the performance of the MiniGames.com website and these companies use their own unique identifiers. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any information if and what these companies collect from our visitors.

We use third-party advertising companies to place their ads in our website. These companies may use behavioral information about our visitors and not personal.

By using this site, you signify that you consent to the MiniGames.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, we advise you not to visit our website. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. You’re advised from time to time to check our Privacy Policy for possible changes and continuing visiting MiniGames.com signifies your acceptance of these changes.
